LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
Here they come.
I will stop Aramaki here.
Tell them that.
Understood, sir.
Come in.
Excuse me.
Chief Niimi, an arrest warrant has been issued
charging you with abetting the homicides
committed during the Sunflower Society investigation
and the assassination of Imakurusu Hisahi.
Please come with me.
I've heard regarding the assault team.
However, do you presume that
I ordered Imakurusu's murder?
Regarding the assault team's squad
leader, Yasuoka Gayle,
he is a surprisingly straightforward man.
it appears that he recorded
his communications with you
and is now being quite cooperative
with our investigation.
I'm sure that we will thoroughly interrogate him regarding the motives
behind Imakurusu's murder and its connection to the Laughing Man case.
All right, then.
I am prepared.
Take him.
CORPORATE
GRAFT
I will return to headquarters for now.
Bomer, be present at Niimi's interrogation.
Pazu, go to the Narcotics Division's
Human Resources Department
and identity the remaining
members of the assault team.
Start there.
Understood.
Councilman... Kanzaki.
I'm indebted to you for saving my daughter.
No, I was only doing my duty.
That aside, why are you here, councilman?
I was "demoted".
I have a lot of time on my hands.
It appears that you are going to use this
opportunity to cut right into the core of the case,
but who do you believe is
above Niimi in the organisation
I'm not a liberty to disclose that information.
No one will hear you.
Was it Secretary-General Yakushima?
Bulls-eye, I see.
Be careful.
He has formidable backing when he needs it.
Although this is not widely known,
he carries quite a lot of weight with the MSDF.
Thank you for your warning.
I'm just talking to myself.
Batou, any results from your investigation into
the identity of the man that gave you the file?
Nothing at the moment.
I see.
We believe that he knows the connection between
the invalidated vaccine and the Laughing Man case.
He is an important witness.
What was he trying to do with
the list of vaccine recipients?
Keep one eye out for possible
answers to that question.
One more thing.
Regarding the reinforced exoskeleton's origin,
there is some information
that is a cause for concern.
I will discuss the details
with you at headquarters.
Let's meet there.
All right.
Was that the Chief?
Yeah. The old man got the guy named Niimi, who
was pulling the strings behind the assault team.
I see.
Maybe there was a point in getting shot after all.
In any case, what is this reinforced exoskeleton?
A toy that the assault team brought out of hiding.
The Major fought that thing.
As a result, her cybernetic body overheated and
now she has to switch into a replacement body.
Is she okay?
Well, she is.
What you said was true.
My eyes were "stolen", too.
I'm going now.
I have a pile of work that I need to do.
I would like you to keep this safe for a while.
This is...!
By any chance,
did you get this from the Laughing Man?
I'm from Public Safety Section 9.
I contacted you recently.
If you're going to come in, then at least knock.
It's bad for my health!
I want the official list of assault team
members, complete with photos.
The Narcotics group follows a principle
of not maintaining a static appearance.
The homeless, musicians, and mafia members...
As such, I can't guarantee that
they're still wearing the same faces.
COMPULSORY REPORT INTO THE NARCOTICS SQUAD
ASSAULT ON THE SUNFLOWER SOCIETY
Must be an easy life as a paper pusher.
You're Aramaki-San from Section 9, right?
I'm sorry, I'm from Kyoto Sports, and-
How did you get in?
Well, I had something I wanted to ask you about.
This man is your brother, correct?
Just yesterday, this Yousuke person was
arrested for illegal narcotics trafficking,
and is now in a police hospital to receive
treatment for a case of serious drug addiction.
Have you heard anything about it?
It does appear to be my brother,
but I have not seen him since
he went MIA during the war.
Can I ask you a few questions?
Oh, hey! The photo!
This is your new body, Motoko?
It's the same as your current one, isn't it?
You should have had it custom made.
I don't care about its appearance.
What is this? They're all illegal options!
Wow, just thinking about them makes me excited!
Er, was it all right for me to be the witness?
I'm sure there won't be any problems.
After all, you do have an official licence.
Can you fasten the back of this for me?
In any case, the doctor is pretty late.
Thanks.
I'll go take a look, okay?
Okay, thanks.
I'm Aramaki from Public Safety Section 9.
I would like to see my brother.
I'm sorry, sir,
but my superiors have ordered that
you are not to be granted
family visitation rights.
I only require three minutes.
I'm just going to confirm facts.
I'm sorry, but these are the regulations.
I see.
My brother...
How is Aramaki Yousuke's condition?
I cannot answer that question either, sir.
I see.
Sorry to have made you wait.
I will be your physician today. My name is Sano.
Oh? This can't be your first time.
I'll make sure it won't hurt, so you'll be fine.
Well then, let's start the diagnosis right away.
Please observe from the viewing area.
This must be your new body.
While the transfer is in progress,
I will deactivate your network functions.
This room will also block all radio
waves until the transfer is complete.
Would you please give me permission to do that?
Get it over with, will you?
I'm in a bit of a hurry.
You're an impatient one, aren't you?
Now then, allow me to inspect your interior...
As expected, you have quite a nice body.
The old man is running late, isn't he?
You've been anxious ever since the
Laughing Man stole your eyes, haven't you?
I was supposed to be here to
get an update from the old man.
I see.
I guess I'll try and track him down.
He was back once already.
He ran an ID check on a newspaper
reporter from the garage.
For what?
This is strange...
Chief has his cyberbrain on autistic mode.
What about the GPS?
His car is in the Shoui
Refugee Residential Sector.
The logs say that it was
parked there three minutes ago.
In a place that dangerous?!
What the hell is he thinking?
I'll go take a look.
You betrayed me!
Yousuke!
Is that you, Yousuke?
Were you able to come back already?
Wow, you're wearing a nice suit.
Is that from you-know-whom?
You know Yousuke?
You're Yousuke's little brother, aren't you?
I could tell right away
because you look just like him.
So, Yousuke was here?
Yeah, although he was taken
away by the police yesterday.
Can you tell me what happened?
Yousuke was respected by everyone.
He was the one who brought order to this place.
Until he did, this place was lawless.
But the police came out of
nowhere and took Yousuke away.
Then, it had nothing to do with
illegal narcotics trafficking?
Of course not!
I recorded what the police did on this disc.
The data should be able to
prove Yousuke's innocence!
Let's save Yousuke!
No signs of tampering.
Does that mean he got off here voluntarily?
Can you pick up footage inside the sector?
I found a log of the security cameras
within the residential sector.
The Chief's meeting with someone.
The resolution is bad.
Can you get rid of the noise?
It may take me a while.
I'm counting on you.
Ishikawa, I've determined the current appearances
of the three remaining members of the assault team.
I'll send you the data.
Understood.
Toss it in.
Just you wait...
I'll deal with all of you in due time.
What do you think you're doing? Let me go!!!
We had a tip-off. Stop resisting!
What are you talking about?
What are you doing?!
You won't find anything!
Found it.
You guys framed me, bastards!
What are you doing?!
Stop resisting!
As I'd thought, the charge was false.
Yeah, the dirty bastards.
They probably wanted a prize and framed Yousuke.
Yousuke never laid a single finger on any drugs.
With this much evidence,
I can prove my brother's innocence.
Thank you. I will repay you for this one day.
Don't bother.
After all... you won't be able
to go back safe and sound!
What?
Major...
I got rid of the noise.
These guys are...!!!
What's wrong?
I'll send the data now!
Hey, this is...!
The Chief was set up!
His cyberbrain's autistic mode was disabled!
The police will be here soon.
You're finished.
Wait a minute... what the hell?
Drugs?!
The situation's not good.
The authorities are rushing to
the Refugee Residential Sector
to make an arrest for red-handed
illegal drug trafficking!
Damn it!
Does your brain hurt?
A humorless joke.
The brain cannot feel pain.
Don't say that.
Let's relax and enjoy this.
Or could it be that you don't like me?
Unfortunately, that is the case.
Now that you know, can you hurry up?
I don't really have time to waste.
My, being a little arrogant, are we?
I limited your speech centre.
Of course, not that anyone will come
to save you even if you were to shout.
Hello, Miss Chrysalis. How do you feel?
My, what rebellious eyes. That won't do.
How is a world without the colour red?
Isn't it pretty?
To tell you the truth,
I don't really want to do such barbaric things,
but you went a bit too far.
The authorities have arrived.
I can see that!
This is the police!
Hey, is this really-
What's going on, damn it?!
Damn it... Hold on, old man!
What is this? Is it to spite me?
Your brainwaves indicate your discomfort.
For now, please use my eyes.
You're the Laughing Man, aren't you?
This is the third time that we've
met, yet you know who I am?
Although they just call me that.
It's quite audacious of you to come here.
Why did you come here?
I came here to be saved by you.
Don't you mean the other way around?
True.
But I'm so beat up right now that this
is the only method I can think of.
I thought that if God or
whatever-powers-that-be hadn't abandoned me,
then he would lend me a hand.
How selfish of you.
Furthermore, you seem polite,
but say things in such a blasphemous manner.
I absolutely cannot afford to lose this time.
if this continues, then all fraud
in the world will be justified.
You sound as if you're shouldering
the weight of the entire world.
Well then, what would the
Net's hero want me to do?
I'm going to tell you the truth
behind the Laughing Man case.
In addition, I would like for you to quietly observe
the last challenge that I am about to make.
If I happen to lose and die, then I would
like you to bring the truth to light.
My, my...
"The mark of the immature man is that
he wants to die nobly for a cause,"
"while the mark of the mature man is
that he wants to live humbly for one."
Words of the psychoanalyst Wilhelm Stekel.
As I thought, you're the type of
person I dislike, Mr. Intellectual.
As if you're not one of the former
considering that I would
save you if you said "help".
Repulsion for one's kin; it can not be helped.
Please do something about this, although I
can't guarantee that I can keep my promise.
You would, being you.
I will leave my memories behind.
I'm counting on you.
Farewell, take care.
Now then, I regret doing this,
but I'll let you go painlessly.
The needles...!
What...?
Nothing.
Major.
What is it?
The old man got hit.
Chief Niimi, it's time for your interrogation.
Chief Niimi?
Chief!
How is your new body?
Just what it looks like.
You look better than I thought you would.
Well, so to speak.
I'm sorry for doing this to you so
soon after regaining consciousness,
but I have some good news and some bad news.
Let's hear the bad news first.
Chief Niimi attempted cyberbrain suicide.
Parts of his speech and memory
centres have lost their functionality.
His testimony is now no longer
admissible in a court of law.
And now, the good news...
Regarding your brother, the charges against him were all
fabricated by residual members of the assault team.
You can't really call that good news, either.
Although it might be true that
your brother was really there.
I have always been eager to
uncover the truth behind crimes,
but the resultant reality is that I did not even notice
that my brother was living under these frigid skies.
I have come this far believing that turning a blind
eye and a deaf ear to those who are close to me
in order to fulfil my
responsibilities was justice.
However, I am not sure anymore if
that was the right thing to do.
And yet you will continue to fight, right?
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up